{
    "subject": "resource/Hermann_Gl\u00f6ckner",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Dresden",
    "human_readable": "Hermann Gl\u00f6ckner was born in Dresden.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9024943113327026,
            "question": "Where was Hermann Gl\u00f6ckner born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7167896628379822,
            "question": "Were there any significant events that happened in Dresden during Hermann Gl\u00f6ckner's lifetime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7022397518157959,
            "question": "What other notable people were born in Dresden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6469623446464539,
            "question": "What city is associated with Hermann Gl\u00f6ckner's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5933651328086853,
            "question": "Are there any details about Hermann Gl\u00f6ckner's life besides his birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4720182418823242,
            "question": "Is there information about Hermann Gl\u00f6ckner's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2470063418149948,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Dresden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23010051250457764,
            "question": "How can we learn more about Hermann Gl\u00f6ckner's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22305689752101898,
            "question": "Is there any connection between Hermann Gl\u00f6ckner and Albert Einstein?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03770521283149719,
            "question": "What is the significance of birthplace in understanding a person's life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hermann Gl\u00f6ckner was born in Dresden.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8409_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any connection between Hermann Gl\u00f6ckner and Albert Einstein?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8409_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How can we learn more about Hermann Gl\u00f6ckner's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8409_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Dresden?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8409_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8409_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8409_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8409_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8409_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8409_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8409_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8409_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8409_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8409_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8409_65.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the information in the documents supports the statement that Hermann Gl\u00f6ckner was indeed born in Dresden, as mentioned in several files (e.g. file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8409/re-ranker-msmarco/5.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8409/re-ranker-msmarco/61.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Hermann Gl\u00f6ckner was born in Dresden.\" Specifically, this is mentioned in multiple texts within the provided files."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}